---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://www.opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
      User-Agent:
      - Ruby
  response:
    status:
      code: 301
      message: Moved Permanently
    headers:
      Date:
      - Thu, 23 Feb 2017 18:25:15 GMT
      Server:
      - Apache
      Location:
      - https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10
      Content-Length:
      - '245'
      Content-Type:
      - text/html; charset=iso-8859-1
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: |
        <!DOCTYPE HTML PUBLIC "-//IETF//DTD HTML 2.0//EN">
        <html><head>
        <title>301 Moved Permanently</title>
        </head><body>
        <h1>Moved Permanently</h1>
        <p>The document has moved <a href="https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10">here</a>.</p>
        </body></html>
    http_version: 
  recorded_at: Thu, 23 Feb 2017 18:25:15 GMT
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
      User-Agent:
      - Ruby
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Date:
      - Thu, 23 Feb 2017 18:25:15 GMT
      Server:
      - Apache
      Expires:
      - Thu, 19 Nov 1981 08:52:00 GMT
      Cache-Control:
      - no-store, no-cache, must-revalidate, post-check=0, pre-check=0
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Access-Control-Allow-Origin:
      - "*"
      Set-Cookie:
      - PHPSESSID=cT8eg3IdgB5CVEAhknd5x2; path=/
      Strict-Transport-Security:
      - max-age=31536000
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The
        Axolotl is an amphibian that can spend its whole life in a larval state.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment:
        Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which of these
        is NOT the name of an album released by Miami-based producer DJ Khaled?","correct_answer":"Don&#039;t
        Ever Play Yourself","incorrect_answers":["Major Key","Suffering From Success","I
        Changed A Lot"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which
        of these &quot;Worms&quot; games featured 3D gameplay?","correct_answer":"Worms
        4: Mayhem","incorrect_answers":["Worms W.M.D","Worms Reloaded","Worms: Open
        Warfare 2"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"medium","question":"In
        &quot;Team Fortress 2&quot;, the &quot;Bill&#039;s Hat&quot; is a reference
        to the game &quot;Dota 2&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Science
        & Nature","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Which of the following
        plastic is commonly used for window frames, gutters and drain pipes?","correct_answer":"Polyvinylchloride
        (PVC) ","incorrect_answers":["Polyethylene (PE)","Polypropylene (PP)","Polystyrene
        (PS)"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"In
        Monster Hunter Generations, which of these hunter arts are exclusive to the
        Longsword?","correct_answer":"Unhinged Spirit","incorrect_answers":["Shoryugeki","Provoke","Demon
        Riot"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Who
        recorded the album called &quot;Down to the Moon&quot; in 1986?","correct_answer":"Andreas
        Vollenweider","incorrect_answers":["Jean-Michel Jarre","Bing Crosby","Enya"]},{"category":"Science:
        Computers","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"Who is the original
        author of the realtime physics engine called PhysX?","correct_answer":"NovodeX","incorrect_answers":["Ageia","Nvidia","AMD"]},{"category":"Sports","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        team won the 2016 MLS Cup?","correct_answer":"Seattle Sounders","incorrect_answers":["Colorado
        Rapids","Toronto FC","Montreal Impact"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video
        Games","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Who is the main
        character in most of the games of the YS series?","correct_answer":"Adol Christin
        ","incorrect_answers":["Character doesn&#039;t have a name","Estelle Bright","Roger
        Wilco"]}]}'
    http_version: 
  recorded_at: Thu, 23 Feb 2017 18:25:15 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 3.0.3
